Well now we're getting somewhere. All we have to do is run those table creation
queries by calling exact sequel at the end of our on create function. But wait,
there's another function in our SQliteOpenHelper, onUpgrade. You might think,
why should I care about those?
I'm not upgrading anything yet. To make our development lives easier we're
going to implement the most standard kind of onUpgrade there is.
You see onUpgrade only fires if you change the version of your database.
Now remember, we passed that version into the SQliteOpenHelper base constructor,
ages ago. Since we are going to be using our database as a cache for web data
and not for user generated content, we'll drop the tables. This is helpful if we
want to change the database in the future. If we were using user data, we'd do
something like use alter table to add new columns. So, now we have a database.